Have you ever looked out a plane window
and wondered, what if I could just
and land on a fluffy cloud? For that to
work, the cloud would need to be about
as dense as you are. And you're about as
dense as water. So, the cloud would need
to be basically a lake floating in the
sky.
And Earth's air is about 800 times too
light to hold that up. So, let's thicken
it. Crank the air 50 times heavier. And
now it's like Venus.
Nope, still too thin. And now the
problem is the harder you squeeze the
air to hold the cloud lake up, the
hotter it gets, which means the faster
the cloud lake boils away. But, there is
a place that could hold it up, deep
inside Jupiter. The air here is squeezed
so hard that the hydrogen turns into
liquid and then into metal.
So, if we turned everything below into
Jupiter, you could land on a fluffy
cloud for a split second until you
vaporize. But, Jupiter's moons are
insane. To see why, subscribe.